<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
	<id>com.jetpackduba.Gitnuro</id>
	<name>Gitnuro</name>
	<summary>Multiplatform Git client</summary>
	<metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
	<project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
	<description>
		<p>
            Gitnuro is a Git client that allows you to manage multiple repositories with a modern experience and live visual representation of your repositories' state.
		</p>
	</description>
	<developer_name>Abdelilah El Aissaoui</developer_name>
	<url type="homepage">https://gitnuro.com</url>
	<launchable type="desktop-id">com.jetpackduba.Gitnuro.desktop</launchable>
	<content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot>
			<image type="source">https://github.com/JetpackDuba/Gitnuro/raw/main/res/img/cover.png</image>
		</screenshot>
	</screenshots>
	<releases>
		<release version="1.3.1" date="2023-10-30">
			<url>https://github.com/JetpackDuba/Gitnuro/releases/tag/v1.3.1</url>
			<description>
				<p>Changes</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Fixed error while pulling or pushing via SSH and using Bitbucket.</li>
					<li>Improved "Stage all" speed in big repositories.</li>
					<li>Fixed "Change upstream branch" crash.</li>
					<li>Fixed constant reloading of log tree due to detection of changes.</li>
					<li>Improved performance when doing large UI operations that may affect a lot of files.</li>
					<li>Fixed diff headers disapearing when cliking on "split diff".</li>
					<li>Fixed buttons being overlapped by text path in the diff header.</li>
					<li>Fixed typo in settings.</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="1.3.0" date="2023-09-26">
			<url>https://github.com/JetpackDuba/Gitnuro/releases/tag/v1.3.0</url>
			<description>
				<p>New features</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Added 175% scale option</li>
					<li>Restored Git directory changes detection</li>
					<li>Proxy support</li>
					<li>Settings UI/UX rework</li>
					<li>Option to set a custom terminal emulator </li>
					<li>Option to view full file in diff</li>
					<li>Added drop and edit to rebase interactive</li>
					<li>Fixed submodules not opening in windows </li>
					<li>Tabs can now be closed when tertiary button (AKA the mouse wheel)</li>
					<li>Option to swap unstaged/staged views order</li>
					<li>Now the last repository opened is remembered</li>
					<li>Force push now uses lease by default</li>
					<li>Added option to specify the directory that will be created during a clone</li>
					<li>Now the tabs are loaded lazily to avoid excessivo IO load when reopening the app and having many repositories open</li>
					<li>Tabs can now be sorted</li>
					<li>Changed settings files path to follow the XDG standard</li>
					<li>HTTP credentials in-memory caching</li>
				</ul>
				<p>Bugfixes</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Fixed crash when trying to push via repository via SSH when lacking necessary rights</li>
					<li>Fixed untracked files not being shown in stashes</li>
					<li>Fixed crash when submodules conflict after a merge</li>
					<li>Fixed submodule diff loading forever</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="1.2.1" date="2023-05-14">
			<url>https://github.com/JetpackDuba/Gitnuro/releases/tag/v1.2.1</url>
			<description>
				<p>Fixes and improvements</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Added missing SSH support for submodules.</li>
					<li>Enabled support by default for all supported formats by libssh (such as RSA).</li>
					<li>Fixed crash on clicking "show password" button for SSH/GPG credentials.</li>
					<li>Fixed size of text field in SSH/GPG credentials dialog to match the rest of the UI.</li>
					<li>Added "show password" button to HttpAuthentication dialog.</li>
					<li>Fixed scroll state behavior for commited changes not being preserved across tabs changes nor being reset when changing between commits.</li>
					<li>Fixed diff scroll position not resetting when selecting different files.</li>
					<li>Temporary files are now always removed when closing the app instead of relying on the OS to do it.</li>
					<li>Added missing reference to LibSSH in the section of used libraries projects to create Gitnuro.</li>
					<li>Updated libssh to 0.10.5.</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="1.2.0" date="2023-05-03">
			<url>https://github.com/JetpackDuba/Gitnuro/releases/tag/v1.2.0</url>
			<description>
				<p>New features</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Submodules support.</li>
					<li>SignOff support.</li>
					<li>GPG support.</li>
					<li>Option to change upstream branch.</li>
					<li>LibSSH integration to support SSH-Agent.</li>
					<li>Button to open terminal.</li>
					<li>Option to edit message when amending.</li>
					<li>Search options for files and branches.</li>
					<li>Option to set pull with rebase as default.</li>
					<li>Added support for ARM.</li>
				</ul>
				<p>Bugfixes</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Fix external credentials manager on Flatpak version</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="1.1.1" date="2022-11-15">
			<url>https://github.com/JetpackDuba/Gitnuro/releases/tag/v1.1.1</url>
			<description>
				<p>UI</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Improved graph visualization so it's easier to follow branches.</li>
					<li>Added noto sans to be the default mono font</li>
				</ul>

				<p>Bugfixes</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Fixed tabs scrollbar handling clicks when it isn't visible. Now clicking on
						the top part of a tab will work as expected.</li>
					<li>Fixed repository state not refreshing if branch checkout has failed after
						creation.</li>
					<li>Fixed images opening in system default image viewer not working.</li>
					<li>Fixed log splitter over-dragging when having density higher than 100%.</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="1.1.0" date="2022-10-29" />
		<release version="1.0.1" date="2022-08-07" />
		<release version="1.0.0" date="2022-08-06" />
		<release version="0.1.1" date="2022-04-07" />
	</releases>
</component>