<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
	<id>com.jetpackduba.Gitnuro</id>
	<name>Gitnuro</name>
	<summary>Multiplatform Git client</summary>
	<metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
	<project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
	<description>
		<p>
            Gitnuro is a Git client that allows you to manage multiple repositories with a modern experience and live visual representation of your repositories' state.
		</p>
	</description>
	<developer_name>Abdelilah El Aissaoui</developer_name>
	<url type="homepage">https://gitnuro.com</url>
	<launchable type="desktop-id">com.jetpackduba.Gitnuro.desktop</launchable>
	<content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot type="default">
			<image type="source">https://github.com/JetpackDuba/Gitnuro/raw/main/res/img/cover.png</image>
			<caption>The Gitnuro main window</caption>
		</screenshot>
	</screenshots>
	<releases>
		<release version="1.4.2" date="2024-11-12">
			<url>https://github.com/JetpackDuba/Gitnuro/releases/tag/v1.4.2</url>
			<description>
				<p>Changes</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Fixed changes detection not working (v1.4.1 regression).</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="1.4.1" date="2024-11-11">
			<url>https://github.com/JetpackDuba/Gitnuro/releases/tag/v1.4.1</url>
			<description>
				<p>Changes</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Fixed pre-commit failure makes commit message disappear.</li>
					<li>Fixed changing git config removes .gitconfig symlink.</li>
					<li>Fixed crash when opening a repository that can't be watched due to some other error.</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="1.4.0" date="2024-10-01">
			<url>https://github.com/JetpackDuba/Gitnuro/releases/tag/v1.4.0</url>
			<description>
				<p>Changes</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Files are now always opened as UTF-8 when discarding hunks.</li>
					<li>Added option to drag and drop items in rebase interactive.</li>
					<li>Graph now supports horizontal scroll using the mouse wheel.</li>
					<li>Added tree structure display for files changes.</li>
					<li>Added new scaling options.</li>
					<li>Added option to disable SSL certificate verification.</li>
					<li>Added close button to file search in (un)committed changes .</li>
					<li>Side panel and (un)commited files panes have their width persisted.</li>
					<li>Improved performance when detecting changes if a lot of files have changed.</li>
					<li>Added custom error message when trying to stash an empty workspace.</li>
					<li>Added positive feedback so the user knows clearly when an action has been completed successfully.</li>
					<li>Recent repositories now are unlimited, can be removed and searched.</li>
					<li>&quot;Open&quot; button in a repository  view shows recent repositories instead of directly opening the file explorer.</li>
					<li>Added very basic syntax highlighting for most popular programming languages.</li>
					<li>Error dialogs now show the stacktrace when double clicking on the error icon.</li>
					<li>Added custom error title to the error dialog depending on what action has failed (instead of a generic title).</li>
					<li>Improved performance when switching between tabs.</li>
					<li>Added option to open log directory in the settings.</li>
					<li>Added tooltip for log avatar and menu entries.</li>
					<li>General UI/UX improvements.</li>
					<li>Improved performance of file system changes detection and SSH auth.</li>
					<li>Pushing branches set the tracking branch configuration if it wasn&#39;t set before.</li>
					<li>Added keybindings to interact with tabs. It is still in early phase so bindings may change before they are properly documented.</li>
					<li>Fixed theme not being changed properly until recomposition when switching between themes that have same value for &quot;isLight&quot; property.</li>
					<li>Reduced saturation of the builtin dark themes.</li>
					<li>Improved focus management. It fixes repo manual refresh not working when switching between tabs.</li>
					<li>Improved how closeable UI components can be closed by pressing ESC (includes file diff).</li>
					<li>Fixed theme file picker not working in MacOS.</li>
					<li>Fixed memory leak during SSH authentication.</li>
					<li>Fixed crash when freeing some SSH resources.</li>
					<li>Fixed rebase interactive &quot;Edit&quot; not taking the previous commit message.</li>
					<li>Fixed GH auth failing if arguments are present in the command config.</li>
					<li>Fixed state not updating properly after a conflicting cherry-pick.</li>
					<li>Fixed header drag in log being too fast in high density displays.</li>
					<li>Fixed rebase/merge remote branch not working in the side panel.</li>
					<li>Fixed clicking on &quot;Uncommited changes&quot; didn&#39;t work.</li>
					<li>Fixed pull error message not being shown properly.</li>
					<li>Fixed pull from specific branch to use user&#39;s configuration instead of merge by default.</li>
					<li>Fixed branch checkout in side panel being executed in previous (after changing current tab).</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="1.3.1" date="2023-10-30">
			<url>https://github.com/JetpackDuba/Gitnuro/releases/tag/v1.3.1</url>
			<description>
				<p>Changes</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Fixed error while pulling or pushing via SSH and using Bitbucket.</li>
					<li>Improved "Stage all" speed in big repositories.</li>
					<li>Fixed "Change upstream branch" crash.</li>
					<li>Fixed constant reloading of log tree due to detection of changes.</li>
					<li>Improved performance when doing large UI operations that may affect a lot of files.</li>
					<li>Fixed diff headers disapearing when cliking on "split diff".</li>
					<li>Fixed buttons being overlapped by text path in the diff header.</li>
					<li>Fixed typo in settings.</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="1.3.0" date="2023-09-26">
			<url>https://github.com/JetpackDuba/Gitnuro/releases/tag/v1.3.0</url>
			<description>
				<p>New features</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Added 175% scale option</li>
					<li>Restored Git directory changes detection</li>
					<li>Proxy support</li>
					<li>Settings UI/UX rework</li>
					<li>Option to set a custom terminal emulator </li>
					<li>Option to view full file in diff</li>
					<li>Added drop and edit to rebase interactive</li>
					<li>Fixed submodules not opening in windows </li>
					<li>Tabs can now be closed when tertiary button (AKA the mouse wheel)</li>
					<li>Option to swap unstaged/staged views order</li>
					<li>Now the last repository opened is remembered</li>
					<li>Force push now uses lease by default</li>
					<li>Added option to specify the directory that will be created during a clone</li>
					<li>Now the tabs are loaded lazily to avoid excessivo IO load when reopening the app and having many repositories open</li>
					<li>Tabs can now be sorted</li>
					<li>Changed settings files path to follow the XDG standard</li>
					<li>HTTP credentials in-memory caching</li>
				</ul>
				<p>Bugfixes</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Fixed crash when trying to push via repository via SSH when lacking necessary rights</li>
					<li>Fixed untracked files not being shown in stashes</li>
					<li>Fixed crash when submodules conflict after a merge</li>
					<li>Fixed submodule diff loading forever</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="1.2.1" date="2023-05-14">
			<url>https://github.com/JetpackDuba/Gitnuro/releases/tag/v1.2.1</url>
			<description>
				<p>Fixes and improvements</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Added missing SSH support for submodules.</li>
					<li>Enabled support by default for all supported formats by libssh (such as RSA).</li>
					<li>Fixed crash on clicking "show password" button for SSH/GPG credentials.</li>
					<li>Fixed size of text field in SSH/GPG credentials dialog to match the rest of the UI.</li>
					<li>Added "show password" button to HttpAuthentication dialog.</li>
					<li>Fixed scroll state behavior for commited changes not being preserved across tabs changes nor being reset when changing between commits.</li>
					<li>Fixed diff scroll position not resetting when selecting different files.</li>
					<li>Temporary files are now always removed when closing the app instead of relying on the OS to do it.</li>
					<li>Added missing reference to LibSSH in the section of used libraries projects to create Gitnuro.</li>
					<li>Updated libssh to 0.10.5.</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="1.2.0" date="2023-05-03">
			<url>https://github.com/JetpackDuba/Gitnuro/releases/tag/v1.2.0</url>
			<description>
				<p>New features</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Submodules support.</li>
					<li>SignOff support.</li>
					<li>GPG support.</li>
					<li>Option to change upstream branch.</li>
					<li>LibSSH integration to support SSH-Agent.</li>
					<li>Button to open terminal.</li>
					<li>Option to edit message when amending.</li>
					<li>Search options for files and branches.</li>
					<li>Option to set pull with rebase as default.</li>
					<li>Added support for ARM.</li>
				</ul>
				<p>Bugfixes</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Fix external credentials manager on Flatpak version</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="1.1.1" date="2022-11-15">
			<url>https://github.com/JetpackDuba/Gitnuro/releases/tag/v1.1.1</url>
			<description>
				<p>UI</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Improved graph visualization so it's easier to follow branches.</li>
					<li>Added noto sans to be the default mono font</li>
				</ul>

				<p>Bugfixes</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Fixed tabs scrollbar handling clicks when it isn't visible. Now clicking on
						the top part of a tab will work as expected.</li>
					<li>Fixed repository state not refreshing if branch checkout has failed after
						creation.</li>
					<li>Fixed images opening in system default image viewer not working.</li>
					<li>Fixed log splitter over-dragging when having density higher than 100%.</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="1.1.0" date="2022-10-29" />
		<release version="1.0.1" date="2022-08-07" />
		<release version="1.0.0" date="2022-08-06" />
		<release version="0.1.1" date="2022-04-07" />
	</releases>
</component>
